<paper id='11' total_num='92' total_score='0.0'>
    <base_info>
        <title>2008年6月大学英语四级</title>
        <category>2</category>
        <creater>1</creater>
        <created_at>2011-09-08 14:12</created_at>
        <updated_at>2011-11-01 16:05</updated_at>
        <description/>
        <category_name>CET-4</category_name>
    </base_info>
    <blocks>
        <block id='19' start_time='2:05' time='30' total_num='1' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>Part I Writing </title>
                <description/>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='1'>Directions: For this part, you are allowed 30 minutes to write a short essay on the topic of Recreational activity？You should write at least 150 words following the outline given below:</part_description>
                <description>生命之重</description></problem>
                <problem id='57' score='0.0' types='5'>
                    <title>&lt;p&gt;1.娱乐活动多种多样&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;2.娱乐活动可能使人们受益，也可能有危害性 &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;3.作为大学生，我的看法。&lt;/p&gt;
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='5' flag='' id='20' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>&lt;p&gt;Abundant recreational activities are available for people to release their strain and stress, ranging from sports to online activities. There is going on a hot debate arguing whether they are good for the public or not, especially for college students.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As for such a question, different people hold different views. Some believe that recreation is helpful if we want to keep healthy physically and mentally. While there also sounds an opposite voice, which claims that activities also bring many problems. For example, some young people are easily addicted to the virtual world online, which affects their study seriously and may lead to worse consequences as well.&lt;/p&gt;
　 &lt;p&gt; As for me, I hold a belief that recreational activities do more good than harm. They do give us a good chance, and efficiency too. As long as we can arrange the time reasonably, they will definitely provide more benefits for us.&lt;/p&gt;
                            </answer>
                            <analysis>vvv</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags> 写作</tags>
                        <description>think 有self</description><words>schedule;congratulation;go;move;kill;attractive</words></question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            <problem id='112' question_type='1'><description>ssss</description><title>fffffffggggggggggggggg((sign))</title><category>2</category><questions><question correct_type='1' flag='0' id='136' score='0.0'><description>fffdddd</description><answer>dddd</answer><questionattrs>sssss;-;dddd;-;ffff;-;ssss</questionattrs><tags> 上市</tags><words>miss</words><analysis>fff</analysis></question></questions></problem><problem id='113' question_type='1'><description>cccvvbbb</description><title>eeeeeeeeeee((sign))dddddddddd</title><category>2</category><questions><question correct_type='1' flag='0' id='137' score='0.0'><description>fffss</description><answer>sssssa</answer><questionattrs>dsss;-;ddd;-;sssssa;-;ass</questionattrs><tags></tags><words></words><analysis>ssd</analysis></question></questions></problem></problems>
        </block>
        <block id='20' start_time='1:35' time='15' total_num='10' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>PartⅡ Reading Comprehension</title>
                <description>Directions:	In this part, you will have 15 minutes to go over the passage quickly and answer the questions on Answer Sheet 1. For questions 1-7, choose the best answer from the four choices marked A), B), C) and D). For questions 8-10, complete the sentences with the information given in the passage.</description>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem id='58' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;p&gt;Media Selection for Advertisements &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After determining the target audience for a product or service, advertising agencies must select the appropriate media for the advertisement. We discuss here the major types of media used in advertising. We focus our attention on seven types of advertising: television, newspapers, radio, magazines, out-of-home, Internet, and direct mail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Television &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television is an attractive medium for advertising because it delivers mass audiences to advertisers. When you consider that nearly three out of four Americans have seen the game show &quot;Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?&quot; you can understand the power of television to communicate with a large audience. When advertisers create a brand, for example, they want to impress consumers with the brand and its image. Television provides an ideal vehicle for this type of communication. But television is an expensive medium, and not all advertisers can afford to use it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television&apos;s influence on advertising is fourfold. First, narrowcasting means that television channels are seen by an increasingly narrow segment of the audience. The Golf Channel, for instance, is watched by people who play golf. Home and Garden Television is seen by those interested in household improvement projects. Thus, audiences are smaller and more homogeneous(具有共同特点的) than they have been in the past. Second, there is an increase in the number of television channels available to viewers, and thus, advertisers.&amp;nbsp;This has also resulted in an increase in the sheer number of advertisements to which audiences are exposed. Third, digital recording devices allow audience members more control over which commercials they watch. Fourth, control over programming is being passed from the networks to local cable operators and satellite programmers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Newspaper&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After television, the medium attracting the next largest annual ad revenue is newspapers. The New York Times, which reaches a national audience, accounts for $1 billion in ad revenue annually. It has increased its national circulation (发行量) by 40% and is now available for home delivery in 168 cities. Locally, newspapers are the largest advertising medium. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newspapers are a less expensive advertising medium than television and provide a way for advertisers to communicate a longer, more detailed message to their audience than they can through television. Given new production techniques, advertisements can be printed in newspapers in about 48 hours, meaning newspapers are also a quick way of getting the massage out. Newspapers are often the most important form of news for a local community, and they develop a high degree of loyalty from local readers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Radio&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Advertising on radio continues to grow. Radio is often used in conjunction with outdoor billboards (广告牌) and the Internet to reach even more customers than television. Advertisers are likely to use radio because it is a less expensive medium than television, which means advertisers can afford to repeat their ads often. Internet companies are also turning to radio advertising. Radio provides a way for advertisers to communicate with audience members at all times of the day. Consumers listen to radio on their way to school or work, at work, on the way home, and in the evening hours.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Two major changes—satellite and Internet radio—will force radio advertisers to adapt their methods. Both of these radio forms allow listeners to tune in stations that are more distant than the local stations they could receive in the past. As a result, radio will increasingly attract target audiences who live many miles apart. &lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Magazines &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Newsweeklies, women’s titles, and business magazines have all seen in increases in advertising because they attract the high-end market. Magazines are popular with advertisers because of the narrow market that they deliver. A broadcast medium such as network television&amp;nbsp;attracts&amp;nbsp;all types of audience members, but magazine audiences are more homogeneous. If you read &quot;Sports Illustrated&quot;, for example, you have much in common with the magazine’s other readers. Advertisers see magazines as an efficient way of reaching target audience members.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Advertisers using the print media - magazines and newspapers - will need to adapt to two main changes. First, the Internet will bring larger audiences to local newspapers. These audiences will be more diverse and geographically dispersed(分散) than in the past. Second,&amp;nbsp;advertisers&amp;nbsp;will have to understand how to use an increasing number of magazines for their target audiences. Although some magazines will maintain national audiences, a large number of magazines will entertain narrower audiences.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Out-of-home advertising&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Out-of-home advertising, also called place-based advertising, has become an increasingly&amp;nbsp;effective&amp;nbsp;way of reaching consumers, who are more active than ever before. &amp;nbsp;Many consumers today do not sit at home and watch television. &amp;nbsp;Using billboards, newsstands, and bus shelters for&amp;nbsp;advertising&amp;nbsp;is an effective way of reaching these on-the-go consumers. More consumers travel longer distances to and from work, which also makes out-of-home advertising effective. &amp;nbsp;Technology has changed the nature of the billboard business, making it a more effective medium than in the past. &amp;nbsp;Using digital printing, billboard companies can print a billboard in 2 hours, compared with 6 days previously. &amp;nbsp;This allows advertisers more variety in the types of messages they create because they can change their messages more quickly.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internet &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;As consumers become more comfortable with online shopping, advertisers will seek to reach this market. As consumers get more of their news and information from the Internet, the ability of television and radio to get the word out to consumers will decrease.&amp;nbsp;The challenge to Internet advertisers is to create ads that audience members remember.&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Internet advertising will play a more prominent role in organizations’ advertising in the near&amp;nbsp;future. Internet audiences tend to be quite homogeneous, but small. Advertisers will have to adjust their methods to reach these audiences and will have to adapt their persuasive strategies to the online medium as well.&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Direct mail&amp;nbsp;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;A final advertising medium is direct mail, which uses mailings to consumers to communicate a client&apos;s message. Direct mail includes newsletters, postcards and special promotions. Direct mail is an effective way to build relationships with consumers. For many businesses, direct mail is the most effective from of advertising.&lt;/p&gt;
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' flag='' id='21' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Television is an attractive advertising medium in that_____________.</description>
                            <answer>A) it has large audiences </answer>
                            <analysis>文章中的小标题可以帮助我们快速定位。这里Television部分的第一句话就回答了这个问题：Television is an attractive medium for advertising because it delivers mass audiences to advertisers. </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) it has large audiences ;-;B) it appeals to housewives ;-;C) it helps build up a company’s reputation ;-;D) it is affordable to most advertisers</questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        <words>schedule;and+so+on;go through</words></question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='347' score='0.0'>
                            <description>With the increase in the number of TV channels_________. </description>
                            <answer>D) the number of TV ads people can see has increased</answer>
                            <analysis>还是在Television的部分，第二段里谈到电视广告的四重影响，其中第二重影响说：Second, there is an increase in the number of television channels available to viewers, and thus, advertisers. This has also resulted in an increase in the sheer number of advertisements to which audiences are exposed. 这里提到频道数量上升，带来的结果是观众所能接触到的广告的绝对数量的上升。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) the cost of TV advertising has decreased ;-;B) the number of TV viewers has increased ;-;C) advertisers’ interest in other media has decreased ;-;D) the number of TV ads people can see has increased</questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='25' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Compared with television, newspapers as an advertising medium_________________. </description>
                            <answer>B) convey more detailed messages </answer>
                            <analysis>Newspaper的第二段中提到Newspapers are a less expensive advertising medium than television and provide a way for advertisers to communicate a longer, more detailed message to their audience than they can through television. 这句话比较了报纸和电视的差别，谈到报纸广告更便宜，与受众的交流时间更长更深入。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) earn a larger annual ad revenue ;-;B) convey more detailed messages ;-;C) use more production techniques ;-;D) get messages out more effectively </questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='349' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Advertising on radio continues to grow because ___________. </description>
                            <answer>C) it provides easy access to consumers </answer>
                            <analysis>Radio部分开头第一句就说到Advertising on radio continues to grow. 说明这一段就是说为什么广播的广告会原来越多。理由有3个：&lt;br&gt;
1. 与户外广告和互联网广告组合可以接触到比电视广告更广泛的受众&lt;br&gt;
2. 便宜&lt;br&gt;
3. 全天候&lt;br&gt;
这里的4个选项只有C谈到了，easy access to consumers意思是更容易接触到消费者。和便宜这个理由是相符合的。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) more local radio stations have been set up ;-;B) modern technology makes it more entertaining ;-;C) it provides easy access to consumers ;-;D) it has been revolutionized by Internet radio. </questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='350' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Magazines are seen by advertisers as an efficient way to___________.</description>
                            <answer>A) reach target audiences </answer>
                            <analysis>Magazines这一部分第一段第二句Magazines are popular with advertisers because of the narrow market that they deliver，就谈到了Magazine受欢迎的理由是narrow market，因此定位受众更有效。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) reach target audiences ;-;B) modern technology makes it more entertaining ;-;C) appeal to educated people.;-;D) convey all kinds of messages</questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='351' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Oui-of-home advertising has become more effective because_______ </description>
                            <answer>B) consumers travel more now than ever before </answer>
                            <analysis>找到这句话就基本可以确定答案了More consumers travel longer distances to and from work, which also makes out-of-home advertising effective. &lt;br&gt;
其中to and from work是指上下班，他们travel longer distance，路程更长。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) billboards can be replaced within two hours ;-;B) consumers travel more now than ever before ;-;C) such ads have been made much more attractive ;-;D) the pace of urban life is much faster nowadays </questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='22' score='0.0'>
                            <description> The challenge to Internet advertisers is to create ads that are___________.</description>
                            <answer>C) easy to remember </answer>
                            <analysis>Internet部分第一段中最后一句： The challenge to Internet advertisers is to create ads that audience members remember.  </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) quick to update ;-;B) pleasant to look at ;-;C) easy to remember ;-;D) convenient to access </questionattrs>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='23' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Internet advertisers will have to adjust their methods to reach audiences that tend to be____________ .</description>
                            <answer>quite homogeneous, but small</answer>
                            <analysis>首先从句子本身看，要填入的部分是that后面的从句内容，句子的作用是用来说明audiences的（叫定语从句）。再在文章中，可以找到下面的句子Internet audiences tend to be quite homogeneous, but small.。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='354' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Direct mail is an effective form of advertising for businesses to develop_________________ .</description>
                            <answer>relationship with consumers</answer>
                            <analysis>分析句子知道我们要填入的是名词或者名词词组，用来说明邮件广告对于企业而言是建立（何种事物）的有效形式。回到原文寻找，我们发现有：Direct mail is an effective way to build relationships with consumers. &lt;br&gt;
其中，build和develop意思相同。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='355' score='0.0'>
                            <description>This passage discusses how advertisers select__________for advertisements.</description>
                            <answer> the appropriate media</answer>
                            <analysis>首先理解句子意思，问的是整篇文章所说的内容是广告主如何选择广告的（   ）。如果要寻找这种有关主旨的信息，一般就在文章开始或结束的地方。这篇文章的开头说道：After determining the target audience for a product or service, advertising agencies must select the appropriate media for the advertisement. </analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>快速阅读</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            </problems>
        </block>
        <block id='111' start_time='' time='' total_num='36' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>Part III	Listening Comprehension</title>
                <description>&lt;mp3&gt;/media/paper/2008_06.mp3&lt;mp3&gt;
                </description>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='2'>Section A Directions:	In this section, you will hear 8 short conversations and 2 long conversations. At the end of each conversation, one or more questions will be asked about what was said. Both the conversation and the questions will be spoken only once. After each question there will be a pause. During the pause, you must read the four choices marked A), B), C) and D), and decide which is the best answer. Then mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='524' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;00:07_00:29&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1561' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A) Give his ankle a good rest.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说Usually ankle injuries heal quickly if you stop regular activities for a while.通常踝关节只要停止一段时间的日常活动就可以恢复了。言外之意就是让男的休息一会儿因此选择A项。而BCD三项都是没有提到的。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Give his ankle a good rest.;-;B) Treat his injury immediately.;-;C) Continue.;-;D) Be careful when climbing steps.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='527' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;00:43_01:03&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='24' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C) In a theater.</answer>
                            <analysis>除了在餐厅找位置不需要票以外，这一题似乎ABC三项都可以选择。但是我们需要抓住男的说出的一个关键词，也就是My seat is in the balcony.这一句中得balcony意思是（电影院等得）楼坐，因此我们就只能选择C项了。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) On a train.;-;B) On a plane.;-;C) In a theater.;-;D) In a restaurant.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='534' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;01:19_01:38&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1580' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>B) A sad occasion</answer>
                            <analysis>文中提到Jay Smith在睡梦中（in the sleep）去世了，这个不能算accident，而且提到了funeral葬礼，因此应该选B。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) A tragic accident.;-;B) A sad occasion;-;C) Smith&apos;s unusual life story.;-;D) Smith&apos;s sleeping problem.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='536' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;01:53_02:17&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1582' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D) Focus on the main points of her lectures.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的的建议是Just concentrate on the important ideas she’s talked about in the class, and ignore the details.BC两项显然是完全没有涉及到的，因此不会选择。A项是一个干扰项，女的的确说道了details但是女的说的是ignore the details也就是说女的的建议是忽略细节，而非A项中所说的注重细节，因此我们只能选择D项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Review the details of all her lessons.;-;B) Compare notes with his classmates.;-;C)Talk with her about his learning problems.;-;D) Focus on the main points of her lectures.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='538' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;02:31_02:54&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1584' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)The woman spilt coffee on the man&apos;s jacket.</answer>
                            <analysis>这是一个整体把握的题目，女的一开始提出付夹克的清洁费，然后男的提到了咖啡污渍，因此我们通过这些可以推断出女的把咖啡泼洒在了男的身上，因此选择D项。A项，男的责怪女的把咖啡泼洒在他身上是不对的，因为男子说这样的事情会发生在任何人身上。B项，男的误解了女子的道歉，这个选项显然不符文意。C项，女的是要付夹克的清洁费而不是咖啡的钱。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) The man blamed the woman for being careless.;-;B)The man misunderstood the woman&apos;s apology.;-;C) The woman offered to pay for the man&apos;s coffee.;-;D)The woman spilt coffee on the man&apos;s jacket.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='542' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;03:10_03:32&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1593' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>B) Hard to understand.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说The plot is so complicated that I really got lost 情节过分复杂，十分费解。男的的回答也表示支持这一观点，因此我们选择B项。对话中并没有提到影片乏味，A项不正确。对话中强调的是情节难懂而不是不够精彩，C项错误。男的讲到的是看过第二遍之后理解了电影，而没有讲到电影不值得看到第二次，D项错误。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Extremely tedious.;-;B) Hard to understand.;-;C) Lacking a good plot.;-;D) Not worth seeing twice.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='544' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;03:47_04:05&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='955' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A) Attending every lecture.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说Now you know why I never miss a lecture 现在你知道我为什么从来不落下任何一次课了吧。意思就是说上课对她取得高分有相当重要的作用，因此我们选择A项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Attending every lecture.;-;B) Doing lots of homework.;-;C) Reading very extensively.;-;D) Using test-taking strategies.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem id='545' question_type='1' score='0.0' types='0'>
                    <title>Selection for Advertisemen((sign))ts &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After determining the target audience for a product or service, advertising((sign)) agencies must select the appropriate media for the advertisement. We discuss here the major types of media used in advertising. We focus our attention on seven types of advertising: television, newspapers, radio, magazines, out-of-home, Internet, and direct mail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Television &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television is an attractive medium ((sign))for advertis((mp3))/mp3/music.mp3((mp3))ing because it delivers((sign)) mass audiences to advertisers. When you consider that nearly three out of four Americans have seen the game show &quot;Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?&quot; you can understand the power of television to communicate with a large audience. When advertisers create a brand, for example, they want to impress consumers with the brand and its image. Television provides an ideal vehicle for this type of communication. But television is an expensive medium, and not all advertisers can afford to use it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television&apos;s influence on advertising is fourfold. First, narrowcasting means ((sign))that television channels are seen by an increasingly narrow segment of the audience. The Golf Channel, for instance, is watched by people who play golf. Home and Garden Television is seen by those interested in household improvement projects. Thus, audiences are smaller and more homogeneous(具有共同特点的) than they have been in the past. Second, there is an increase in the number of television channels available to viewers, and thus, advertisers.&amp;nbsp;This has also resulted in an increase in the sheer number of advertisements to which audiences are exposed. Third, digital recording devices allow audience members more control over which commercials they watch. Fourth, control over programming is being passed from the networks to local cable operators and satellite programmers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Newspaper((sign));
&lt;p&gt;After television, the medium attracting the ne</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='899' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)The new TV system may not provide anything better.</answer>
                            <analysis>男的说I doubt that will have anything different from what we watch now.男的质疑新的系统是否会提供和现在不一样的节目因此选择D项。A项与男的表述的意思完全相反，不能选择，BC两项并没有提及因此不能选择。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)The digital TV system will offer different programs.;-;B)He is eager to see what the new system is like.;-;C)He thinks it unrealistic to have 500 channels.;-;D)The new TV system may not provide anything better.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                         <question correct_type='3' id='1638' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>labor</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='5' id='1639' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>ingredients</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1640' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>vital </answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1641' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>individuals</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1642' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>engage</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='3'>Questions 19 to 22 are based on the conversation you have just heard.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='548' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;05:00_08:10&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='967' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C) the description of a thief in disguise.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说In the paper,says there’s a man going round pretending he is from the electricity board. he steals their money, handbag, whatever, and makes off with it.根据女的说的这两句我们可以判断选择C项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)a notice by the electricity board.;-;B) ads promoting electric appliances.;-;C) the description of a thief in disguise.;-;D) a new policy on pensioners’ welfare.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1600' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)showing them his ID.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说Especially if they flashed a card to you.尤其是在他们向你出示相关证件的时候你就更加不会怀疑他们，因此我们可以判断这个小偷是通过出示证件获取进一步的信任的，故选择D项。BC两项是对话中没有提及的，A项口音为题文章中讲到的是这个小偷有轻微北方口音并非题干中所说的通过正确的口音获取信任，因此ABC三项都是错误的。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)speaking with a proper accent.;-;B)wearing an official uniform.;-;C)making friends with them;-;D)showing them his ID.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1601' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C)not to let anyone in without an appointment.</answer>
                            <analysis>对话中讲到the police are warning people especially pensioners not to admit anyone unless they have an appointment.除非是预约，否则不要让任何人进入家里。故选择C项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)to be on the alert when being followed.;-;B)not to leave senior citizens alone at home.;-;C)not to let anyone in without an appointment.;-;D)to watch out for those from the electricity board.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1602' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C)the pension she had just drawn was stolen.</answer>
                            <analysis>对话中关于老太太的描述是she’s just been to the post office to draw her pension, when he called, she said he must follow her home. He stole the whole lot.也就是说老太的退休金都被偷走了因此选择C项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)she was robbed near the parking lot.;-;B)all her money in the bank disappeared.;-;C)the pension she had just drawn was stolen.;-;D)she was knocked down in the post office.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='4'>Question 23 to 25 are based on the passage you have just heard.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='551' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;08:24_11:10&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1607' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A)marketing consultancy.</answer>
                            <analysis>当男的问女的第一份工作是什么的时候女的的回答是I was a marketing consultant，因此我们选择A项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)marketing consultancy.;-;B)Professional accountancy.;-;C)luxury hotel management.;-;D)business conference organization</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1608' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)being able to speak japanese.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说As I speak Japanese, I had a very big advantage.因为我会说日语，这给了我巨大的优势，因此我们选择D项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)having a good knowledge of its customs.;-;B)knowing some key people in tourism.;-;C)having been to the country before.;-;D)being able to speak japanese.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1609' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A)it will bring her potential into full play.</answer>
                            <analysis>女的说I love train travel. That’s why I am very interested in this job.我喜欢火车旅行，这就是我对这份工作感兴趣的原因。因此女的是因为，可以讲兴趣与工作结合在一起才选择这份工作，所以A项比较符合这一点。B项具有一定的干扰性，虽然工作中包含了火车旅行，但是并没有说到火车旅行的次数，因此不正确。CD两项则没有提及。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)it will bring her potential into full play.;-;B)it will involve lots of train travel.;-;C)it will enable her to improve her chinese.;-;D)it will give her more chances to visit japan.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='5'>Section B&lt;br&gt;
Directions:	In this section, you will hear 3 short passages. At the end of each passage, you will hear some questions. Both the passage and the questions will be spoken only once. After you hear a question, you must choose the best answer from the four choices marked A), B), C) and D). Then mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passage One &lt;br&gt;Questions 26 to 28 are based on the passage you have just heard.
                    </part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='553' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;12:03_15:10&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1614' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A) The lack of time</answer>
                            <analysis>文章中My every day is a race against the clock that I never ever seem to win我总是在与时间赛跑但是却总是输给了实践，类似的话还有好多，由此我们可以推断作者主要抱怨的是缺乏实践，故选择A项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) The lack of time;-;B) The quality of life.;-;C) The frustrations at work.;-;D) The pressure on working families.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1615' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A)They were just as busy as people of today.</answer>
                            <analysis>文章中作者关于祖先是这样说的complained about how little time they had to paint battle scenes on their cave walls.因此他认为先人和我们一样也是非常繁忙感觉缺乏实践的故选择A项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)They were just as busy as people of today.;-;B)They saw the importance of collective efforts.;-;C)They didn’t complain as much as modern man.;-;D)They lived a hard life by hunting and gathering.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1616' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)To find effective ways to give employees flexibility.</answer>
                            <analysis>文章中They set out to find and award the employers who employ the most creative and most effective ways to give their workers flexibility.因此选择D项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)To look for creative ideas of awarding employees.;-;B)To explore strategies for lowering production costs.;-;C)To seek new approaches to dealing with complaints.;-;D)To find effective ways to give employees flexibility.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='6'>          Passage Two&lt;br&gt;
Question 29 to 31 are based on the passage you have just heard.
                    </part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='554' question_type='1' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;15:25_18:22&lt;time&gt;election for Advertisemen((sign))ts &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;After determining the target audience for a product or service, advertising((sign)) agencies must select the appropriate media for the advertisement. We discuss here the major types of media used in advertising. We focus our attention on seven types of advertising: television, newspapers, radio, magazines, out-of-home, Internet, and direct mail. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&lt;p&gt;Television &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television is an attractive medium ((sign))for advertis((mp3))/mp3/music.mp3((mp3))ing because it delivers((sign)) mass audiences to advertisers. When you consider that nearly three out of four Americans have seen the game show &quot;Who Wants to Be a Millionaire?&quot; you can understand the power of television to communicate with a large audience. When advertisers create a brand, for example, they want to impress consumers with the brand and its image. Television provides an ideal vehicle for this type of communication. But television is an expensive medium, and not all advertisers can afford to use it. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Television&apos;s influence on advertising is fourfold. First, narrowcasting means ((sign))that television channels are seen by an increasingly narrow segment of the audience. The Golf Channel, for instance, is watched by people who play golf. Home and Garden Television is seen by those interested in household improvement projects. Thus, audiences are smaller and more homogeneous(具有共同特点的) than they have been in the past. Second, there is an increase in the number of television channels available to viewers, and thus, advertisers.&amp;nbsp;This has also resulted in an increase in the sheer number of advertisements to which audiences are exposed. Third, digital recording devices allow audience members more control over which commercials they watch. Fourth, control over programming is being passed from the networks to local cable operators and satellite programmers.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;br&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&amp;nbsp;Newspaper((sign));
&lt;p&gt;After television, the medium attracting the</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='968' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>B)his children&apos;s efforts.</answer>
                            <analysis>Raising 6 children during the difficult times of the Great Depression took its toll on my parents’ relationship and resulted in their divorce 六个孩子的抚养负担造成了父母见的关系变差导致离婚，因此选择B项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)family violence. ;-;B)his children&apos;s efforts.;-;C)her father&apos;s disloyalty;-;D)his second wife’s positive influence.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1618' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>D)his second wife&apos;s positive influence.</answer>
                            <analysis>It was because of our other mother, daddy’s second wife, that he became closer to his own children.因为父亲的第二任妻子，父亲与孩子的关系开始变得比以前亲密起来。因此选择D项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)his advanced age.;-;B)his children’s efforts.;-;C) his improved financial condition.;-;D)his second wife&apos;s positive influence.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1619' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>B)love breeds love.</answer>
                            <analysis>后母通过自己对孩子的爱，获得了孩子们对她的爱，爱会带来爱，因此我们选择B项。其实文章的开头也表达了这一观点。这种大意概括累的题目应该抓住文章的开头和结尾。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)love is blind.;-;B)love breeds love.;-;C)divorce often has disastrous consequences.;-;D)happiness is hard to find in blended families.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='7'>          Passage Three&lt;br&gt; Questions 32 to 35 are based on the passage you have just heard.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='556' question_type='1' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;18:37_21:51&lt;time&gt;</title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1623' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>B)its owner died of a heart attack.</answer>
                            <analysis>Just as suddenly, the owner of the greenhouse where I worked as manager died of a heart attack.故选择B</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)it was located in a park.;-;B)its owner died of a heart attack.;-;C)it went bankrupt all of a sudden.;-;D)its potted plants were for lease only.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1624' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C)putting up a going out of business sign.</answer>
                            <analysis>Then one morning, as I was hanging out “Going out of Business” sign at the greenhouse, the door opened and in walked a customer.故选择C</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)planting some trees in the greenhouse.;-;B)writing a want ad to a local newspaper.;-;C)putting up a going out of business sign.;-;D)helping a customer select some purchases.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1625' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>C)developing fresh business opportunities.</answer>
                            <analysis>Why was I helping her select her purchases? My mind was racing. Perhaps as many as a dozen firms have recently opened offices in the new office park, and there were several hundred more acres with construction under way作者思考还有许多公司需要类似的服务，因此觉得发现了巨大的上级，选择C项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)opening an office in the new office park.;-;B)keeping better relations with her company.;-;C)developing fresh business opportunities.;-;D)buliding a big greenhouse of his own.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1626' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>A)owning the greenhouse one day </answer>
                            <analysis>And one day, we hope to be the proud owners of the greenhouse.因此选择A项。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A)owning the greenhouse one day ;-;B)securing a job at the office park.;-;C)cultivating more potted plants.;-;D)finding customers out of town.</questionattrs>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='8'>          Section C&lt;br&gt;Directions:	In this section, you will hear a passage three times. When the passage is read for the first time, you should listen carefully for its general idea. When the passage is read for the second time, you are required to fill in the blanks numbered from 36 to 43 with the exact words you have just heard. For blanks numbered from 44 to 46 you are required to fill in the missing information. For these blanks, you can either use the exact words you have just heard or write down the main points in your own words. Finally, when the passage is read for the third time, you should check what you have written.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='558' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;time&gt;23:02_33:00&lt;time&gt;&amp;nbsp;&amp;nbsp; &lt;br&gt;We’re now witnessing the emergence of an advanced economy based on information and knowledge. Physical(36)___, raw materials, and capital are no longer the key(37) ____ in the creation of wealth. Now, the(38) ____ raw material in our economy is knowledge. Tomorrow&apos;s wealth depends on the development and exchange of knowledge. And(39) ___ entering the workforce offer their knowledge, not their muscles. Knowledge workers get paid for their education and their ability to learn. Knowledge workers(40)____ in mind work.
They deal with symbols: words,(41) ___ and data.What does all this mean for you? As a future knowledge worker, you can expect to be(42)____,processing,as well as exchanging information.(43)____, three out of four jobs involve some form of mind work,and that number will increase sharply in the futhure. Mannagement and employees alike(44)_____.In the new world od work, you can look forward to being in constant training(45)_____.You can also expect to be taking greater control of your career. Gone are the nine-five jobs. lifetime security, predictable promotions, and even the conventional workplace, as you are familiar with.(46)____.And don&apos;t wait for someone to “empower” you. You have to empower yourself.&lt;/time&gt;&lt;/time&gt;
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1638' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>labor</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='5' id='1639' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>ingredients</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1640' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>vital </answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1641' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>individuals</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1642' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>engage</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1643' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>figures </answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1644' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>generating</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1645' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>Currently </answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1646' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>will be making decisions in such areas as product development, quality control, and customer satisfaction</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1647' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>to acquire new skills that will help you keep up with improved technologies and procedures.</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='1648' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>Don’t expect the companies will provide you with a clearly defined career path</answer>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>听力</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            </problems>
        </block>
        <block id='116' start_time='' time='' total_num='20' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>Part IV Reading Comprehension</title>
                <description/>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='9'>          Section A &lt;br&gt;Directions:	In this section, there is a passage with ten blanks. You are required to select one word for each blank from a list of choices given in a word bank following the passage. Read the passage through carefully before making your choices. Each choice in the bank is identified by a letter. Please mark the corresponding letter for each item on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre. You may not use any of the words in the bank more than once.&lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Questions 47 to 56 are based on the following passage.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='566' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>Some years ago I was offered a writing assignment that would require three months of travel through Europe. I had been abroad a couple of times, but I could hardly ____47____ to know my way around the continent. Moreover, my knowledge of foreign languages was ____48____ to a little college French.
&lt;br&gt;I hesitated. How would I, unable to speak the language,____49____ unfamiliar with locatl geography or transportation systems, set up ____50____ and do research? It seemed impossible, and with considerable ____51____ I sat down to write a letter begging off. Halfway through, a thought ran through my mind: you can’t learn if you don&apos;t try. So I accepted the assignment. There were some bad ____52____.But by the time I had finished the trip I was an experienced traveler. And ever since, I have never hesitated to head for even the most remote of places. Without guides or even ____53____ bookings, confident that somehow I will manage. The point is that the new, the different, is almost by definition ____54____.But each time you try something, you learn, and as the learning piles up, the world opens to you. I&apos;ve learned to ski at 40, and flown up the Rhine River in a ____55____.And I know I&apos;ll go to
doing such things. It’s not because I&apos;m braver or more daring than others. I’m not. But I’ll accept anxiety as another name for challenge and I believe I can ____56____ wonders.
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1665' score='0.0'>
                            <answer> claim</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  动词辨认题。空格处缺少动词原形。根据句意，意为“声称”。 D)claim比较随意，可以表示“个人的声明，宣称”；claim to do表示“宣称做某事”。A）accomplish“完成”；F）declare“宣布（法律、公告等），声明”；M）regret“遗憾，抱歉”，词义不符。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs> claim;-;constantly</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1666' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>limited</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  句法推断题。空格位于系动词was之后，介词to之前，因此缺少形容词或者过去分词，可用于be...to 的搭配。be limited to表示“局限于”。 L)reduced表示“减少”，不能与to搭配。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>limited;-;declare</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1667' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>totally</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  副词辨认题。用于形容词之前，空格处缺少副词。根据句意，表示“完全地”。选项中的另一个副词E）constantly“经常地”，不符合句意。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>totally;-;manufacture</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1668' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>interviews</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  名词辨析题。空格处缺少名词，与research并列，因此选择G）interviews“采访”。选项中的另三个名词C）balloon“气球”， J）moments“时刻”， K）news“新闻，消息”，不符合句意，排除。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>interviews;-;news</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1669' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>regret</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  名词辨析题。空格前有形容词considerable，这里需要填名词。regret“抱歉，遗憾”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>regret;-;reduced</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1670' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>moments</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  名词辨析题。空格位于形容词bad之后，需要名词，根据句意，这里表示“沮丧、糟糕的时候”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>moments</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1671' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>advanced </answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  形容词辨析题。空格位于名词bookings之前，缺少形容词或者过去分词。修饰bookings“预约”，所填词应表示“提前的”。其他分词、形容词选项L）reduced“减少的”，N) scary“引起惊慌的”，意义不符。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>advanced </questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1672' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>scary</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  名词辨析题。空格处需要形容词，表示“令人害怕的，引起惊慌的”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>scary</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1673' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>balloon</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  动词辨析题。空格位于不定冠词之后，因此缺少名词。根据句意应选C）balloon“气球”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>balloon</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='6' id='1674' score='0.0'>
                            <answer>accomplish</answer>
                            <analysis>【精析】  动词辨析题。空格位于情态动词can之后，名词wonders之前，缺少动词原形。根据句意A）accomplish“实现, 完成”符合句意。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>accomplish</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='10'>          Section B &lt;br&gt;Directions:	There are 2 passages in this section. Each passage is followed by some questions or unfinished statements. For each of them there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D). You should decide on the best choice and mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre. &lt;br&gt;&lt;br&gt;Passage One &lt;br&gt;Questions 57 to 61 are based on the following passage.</part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='570' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>Global warming may or may not be the great environmental crisis of the 21st century, but- regardless of whether it is or isn&apos;t - we won&apos;t do much about it. We will argue over it and may even, as a nation, make some fairly solemn-sounding commitments to avoid it. But the more dramatic and meaningful these commitments seem, the less likely they are to be observed.&lt;br&gt;
	Al Gore calls global warming an &quot;inconvenient truth,&quot; as if merely recognizing it could put us on a path to a solution. But the real truth is that we don&apos;t know enough to relieve global warming, and - without major technological breakthroughs - we can&apos;t do much about it.&lt;br&gt;
	From 2003 to 2050,the world&apos;s population is projected to grow from 6.4 billion to 9.1 billion, a 42% increase.If energy use per person and technology remain te same, total energy use and greenhouse gas emissions(mainly, CO2) will be 42% higher in 2050. But that’s too low, because societies that grow richer use more energy. We need economic growtht unless we condemn the world&apos;s poor to their persent poverty and freeze everyone else&apos;s living standards.With modest growth, energy use and greenhouse emissions more than double by 2050.&lt;br&gt;
	No government will adopt rigid restrictions on economic growth and personal freeom (limits on electrity usage, driving and travel)that might cut bach global warming. Still, politicians want to show they’re “doing something.” Consider the Kyoto Protocol(京都议定书). It allowed countries that joined to punish those that didn&apos;t. But it hasn&apos;t reduced CO2 emissions(up about 25% since 1990), and many signatories(签字国) didn&apos;t adopt tough enough policies to hit their 2008-2012 targets. The practical conclusion is that if global warming is a potential disaster, the only solution is new technology. Only an aggressive research and development program might find ways of breaking our dependence on fossil fuels or dealing with it. The trouble with the global warming debate is that it has become a moral proble when it’s really an engineering one. The inconvenient truth is that if we don’t solve the engineering problem, we’re helpless.
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1687' score='0.0'>
                            <description>What is said about global warming in the first paragraph?</description>
                            <answer>D) Very little will be done to bring it under control</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 细节辨认题。由题干中所提及到的in the first paragraph可以将题目的答案迅速定位到文章第一段第一句后半部分：but—regardless of whether it is or isn&apos;t—we won&apos;t do much about it.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  根据文章第一句得知，全球变暖有可能成为21世纪的环境危机，但是无论结果如何， 我们都将无能为力。D)中Very little will be done与原文we won&apos;t do much about it意义一致。A)“全球变暖根本不可能引起环境危机”，是对文章第一句的片面理解；B)“全球变暖问题需要全世界范围的努力”，作者在文中提到了这方面 的内容，但是作者的意图重在后半句，也就是说国家承诺越多，执行得越不到位，该句为第一句服务，因此也不是第一段的主旨；C)“已经采取了严格的措施来避 免或阻止这一问题的发生”，在第一段中根本没有涉及。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) It may not prove an environmental crisis at all.;-;B) It is an issue requiring worldwide commitments.;-;C) Serious steps have been taken to avoid or stop it.;-;D) Very little will be done to bring it under control</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1688' score='0.0'>
                            <description>According to the author&apos;s understanding, what is Al Gore&apos;s view on global warming?</description>
                            <answer>C) It is a problem that can be solved once it is recognized.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的人名Al Gore可定位到第二段第一句：...as if merely recognizing it could put us on a path to a solution.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  语义理解题。题目问的是Al Gore对全球变暖的看法。好像只要意识到它，就可以找到解决这一问题的方法。C）与此表述一致。A）“它是一个平民和政客们共识的问题”，显然是对第一句中as if 引导的句子的错误理解；B）“这是一个导致很多不便的现象”，是对“inconvenient truth”的表面理解，排除；D）是作者的看法，不是Al Grore 的看法。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) It is a reality both people and politicians are unawre of.;-;B) It is a phenomenon that causes us many inconveniences .;-;C) It is a problem that can be solved once it is recognized.;-;D) It is an area we actually have little knowledge about.</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1689' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Greenhouse emissions will more than double by 2050 because of ___.</description>
                            <answer>A) economic growth</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的more than double by 2050定位到第三段末句：With modest growth, energy use and greenhouse emissions more than double by 2050.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  细节辨认题。按照一个较为中等的增长速度来看，能量消耗和温室气体排放到2050年时将是现在的两倍多。A)economic growth即原文中的growth。B）“能源的浪费”，文中没有涉及能源浪费问题；C）“贫富之间差距的加大”，文中所涉及的让穷人维持现状，意在说 明经济的停滞，而非贫富之间的差距加大，当然也不会有题干的结果；D）“科技的突飞猛进”，作者在该段第二句中提到：If energy use per person and technology remain the same, 其实也是在表明科技的进步会促进经济的发展，因此它不是导致题干结果的直接原因。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) economic growth;-;B) wasteful use of energy;-;C) the widening gap between the rich and poor;-;D) the rapid advances of science and technology</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1690' score='0.0'>
                            <description>The author believes that, since the signing of the Kyoto Protocol,____.</description>
                            <answer>B) few nations have adopted real tough measures to limit energy use</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 根据题干中的 the signing of the Kyoto Protocol 定位到原文第四段最后一句：...and many signatories didn&apos;t adopt tough enough policies...&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  细节辨认题。允许缔约国惩罚非缔约国，但它却不能减少排放量，很多签字国也未能采取足够强硬的政策。B)中few nations have adopted real tough measures 和本段最后一句中didn&apos;t adopt enough policies 意义相符。该段第一句说明任何国家都不想限制经济的发展，同时任何政客都想“有所作为”，他们的“作为”主要体现在经济的发展上，而不是控制全球气温变 化，排除A）；降低能源的消耗可以在很大程度上减少这一问题的加剧，但是，这个与《京都议定书》的关系本段没有涉及，排除C）；D）国际合作会有助于这一 问题的解决，实际上作者之所以说到《京都议定书》的签订，意在表明，即便是有这样的合作也没有对此问题的解决作出贡献，相反还加剧了，因为CO2的排放量 较之以前增加了约25％，排除。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) politicians have started to do something to better the situation;-;B) few nations have adopted real tough measures to limit energy use;-;C) reductions in energy consumption have greatly cut back global warming;-;D) international cooperation has contrib</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1691' score='0.0'>
                            <description>What is the message the author intends to convey?</description>
                            <answer>B) The ultimate solution to global warming lies in new technology.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的convey一词可以定位到文章倒数第二段conclusion一词，此处是作者得出结论之处，也是撰写本文的意图。&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  主旨大意题。作者第一段提出问题：面对全球变暖，我们将无能为力。第二段中作者谈到认识到这一问题并不代表找到解决方案，然后提出论点：and—without major technological breakthroughs—we can&apos;t do much about it.第三段讲到全球变暖原因：人口增长和经济发展，并预测未来发展趋势。第四段认为政府行为收效甚微。第五和第六段重申论点：the only solution is new technology. B)是对全文的高度概括，与作者观点相同。A）是对文章最后一段第一句的曲解；作者提到现在我们争论的焦点往往集中在这一问题的解决上，而没有提到这一争论会促进科技的进步，排除C）；D）让我们抛弃某些物质享受而阻止全球气温上升这一问题的发生，文章没有涉及。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Global warming is more of a moral issue than a practical one.;-;B) The ultimate solution to global warming lies in new technology.;-;C) The debate over global warming will lead to technological breakthroughs.;-;D) People have to give up certain materia</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
                <problem>
                    <part_description part_id='11'>          Passage Two&lt;br&gt;
Question 62 to 66 are based on the following passage.
                    </part_description>
                </problem>
                <problem id='574' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title>Someday a siranger will read your e-mail without your permission or scan the Website
you&apos;ve visited，Or perhaps someone will casually glance through your credit card
purchases or cell phonebills to find out your shopping preferences or calling habits.
In fact, it&apos;s likely some of these things have already happened to you. Who would watch
you without your permisson? It might be a spous, a girlfreiend, a marketing company, a
boss, a cop or a criminal. Whoever it is, they will see you in a way you never intended to be seen - the 21st century equivalent of being caught naked.&lt;br&gt;
	Psychologists tell us boundaries are healthy, that it&apos;s important to reveal yourself to friends, family and lovers in stages, at appropriate times. But few boundaries remain. The digital bread crumbs(碎屑)you leave everywhere make it easy for strangers to reconstruct who you are, where you are and what you like. In some cases, a simple Google search can reveal what you think. Like it or not, increasingly we live in a world where you simply cannot keep a secret.&lt;br&gt;
	The key question is: Does that matter? For many Americans, the answer apparently is “no.” When opinion polls ask Americans &lt;br&gt;
	about privacy, most say they are concerned about losting it. A survery found an overwhelming pessimism about privacy, with 60 percent of respondents saying they feel their privacy is “slipping away, and that bothers me.”&lt;br&gt;
	But people say one thing and do another. Only a tiny fraction of Americans change any behaviors in an effort to preserver their privacy. Few people turn down a discount at tollbooths(收费站)to avoid using the EZ-Pass system that can track automobile movements. And few turn down supermarket loyalty cards. Privacy economist A lessandro movements. And few turn down supermarket loyalty cards. Privacy economist A lessandro Acquisti has run a series of tests that reveal people will surrender personal information like Social Security numbers just to get their hands on a pitiful 50-cents-off coupon(优惠券).&lt;br&gt;
	But privacy does matter-at least sometimes. It&apos;s like health: When you have it, you don’t motice it. Only when it’s gone do you wish you’d done more to protect it.
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1704' score='0.0'>
                            <description>What does the author mean by saying &quot;the 21st century equivalent of being caught naked&quot; (Lines 3-4,Para.2)?</description>
                            <answer>A) People &apos;s personal information is easily accessed without their knowledge.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中“the 21st century equivalent of being caught naked”定位到文章第二段最后一句。   &lt;br&gt;
【精析】   语义理解题。根据第一段：我们得知有人会在未经允许的情况下窃取我们的个人信息，电子邮件、网页、信用卡购物清单及电话账单等个人信息赤裸裸地暴露给陌生 人，毫无遮掩。A）中的 is easily accessed without their knowledge与原文中的 watch you without your permission同义。文章中虽然提到我们的个人隐私很容易被别人窃取，但这不表明21世纪的我们在想尽一切办法来窥探别人的隐私，因此排除 B）；C）“人们在信息时代更加坦诚”，这是对我们的隐私容易被窃取的曲解；本文是在讲述信息时代人们的隐私保护问题，这与抓犯罪分子是不同的，排除 D）。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) People &apos;s personal information is easily accessed without their knowledge.;-;B) In the 21st century people try every means to look into others&apos; secrets.;-;C) People tend to be more frank with each other in the information age.;-;D) Criminals are easily</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1705' score='0.0'>
                            <description>What would psychologists advise on the relationships between friends?</description>
                            <answer>C) There should be a distance even between friends.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的psychologists定位到第三段第一句：Psychologists tell us boundaries are healthy, that it&apos;s important to reveal yourself to friends, family and lovers in stages, at appropriate times.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  细节辨认题。心理学家告诉我们，与他人保持一定的界限是有益的。在适合的时候，不同程度地向朋友、家人倾诉是很重要的。但是有些界限是需要保留的。C）中的distance与原文中的boundaries同义，跟本段第二句 but few boundaries remain 意义一致。A）和B)是都是对朋友间该坦诚相待，敞开心扉的陈述，这与“心理学家要求我们在适当的时候，不同程度的袒露心扉”意义相悖，排除；D）项中说朋友间该减少争执，这与心理学家所说的彼此间保持界限不符合。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Friends should open their hearts to each other.;-;B) Friends should always be faithful to each other.;-;C) There should be a distance even between friends.;-;D) There should be fewer disputes between friends.</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1706' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Why does the author say &quot;we live in a world where you simply cannot keep a secret&quot; (Line5,para.3)</description>
                            <answer>B) People leave traces around when using modern technology.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中引用的文字可以定位到文章的第三段最后三句。&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  因果关系题。第三段最后三句指出：在数字时代我们的任何行动都可能暴露个人隐私。我们正生活在一个连秘密都不能保守的世界。B）中的trace与原文中的digital bread crumbs所暗示的意思相同。本文讲的是我们隐私的保护问题，对于现代社会是否是开放的，没有涉及，排除A)。文章也没有提到有人总是对别人的隐私好奇，也没有谈到搜索工具是如何赚钱的，排除C)和D）。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Modern society has finally evolved into an open society.;-;B) People leave traces around when using modern technology.;-;C) There are always people who are curious about others&apos; affairs.;-;D) Many search engines profit by revealing people&apos;s identities.</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1707' score='0.0'>
                            <description>What do most Americans do with regard to privacy protection?</description>
                            <answer>D) They talk a lot but hardly do anything about it.</answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的Americans和privacy定位到第七段第一句：But people say one thing and do another.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  语义理解题。由本句可知人们言行不一。随后举例说明，美国人为了一点利益而提供个人信息。D）符合题意。由第七段第二句:Only a tiny fraction of American change any behaviors in an effort to preserve their privacy可以排除A）；优惠卡的使用是在说美国人会因为小利而透露个人隐私，而不是说明他们总是在商业交易中使用该卡，故排除B）；文中没有涉及他们过度依赖电子设备的内容，C）也排除。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) They change behaviors that might disclose their identity.;-;B) They use various loyalty cards for business transactions.;-;C) They rely most and more on electronic devices.;-;D) They talk a lot but hardly do anything about it.</questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='1708' score='0.0'>
                            <description>According to the passage, privacy is like health in that ___.</description>
                            <answer>D) people don’t cherish it until they lose it  </answer>
                            <analysis>【定位】 由题干中的privacy is like health 定位到末段最后两句：It&apos;s like health: when you have it, you don&apos;t notice it. Only when it&apos;s gone do you wish you&apos;d done more to protect it.&lt;br&gt;
【精析】  推理判断题。作者把隐私同健康作比较，当拥有时，不曾注意到它，一旦失去才知其珍贵。D）中cherish同 wish you&apos;d have done more 意义一致。拿隐私与健康相比仅是为了说明对失去东西的后悔之意，而不是在表明我们保护隐私就像保护健康一样，排除A）；当然也不是不明白它很重要而且容易失去，因此排除B）和C）。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) people will make every effort to keep it.;-;B) its importance is rarely understood;-;C) is is something that can easily be lost;-;D) people don’t cherish it until they lose it  </questionattrs>
                            <tags/>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            </problems>
        </block>
        <block id='23' start_time='0:20' time='15' total_num='20' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>Part V Cloze </title>
                <description>Directions:	There are 20 blanks in the following passage. For each blank there are four choices marked A), B), C) and D) on the right side of the paper. You should choose the ONE that best fits into the passage. Then mark the corresponding letter on Answer Sheet 2 with a single line through the centre.</description>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem id='69' score='0' types='4'>
                    <title>&lt;p&gt;Universities are institutions that teach a wide variety of subjects at advanced levels.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;nbsp;They also carry out research work aimed -68- extending man&apos;s knowledge of these subjects. The emphasis given to each of these functions -69- from university to university, according to the views of the people in -70- and according to the resources available. The smaller and newer universities do no -71- the staff or equipment to carry out the -72- research projects possible in larger institutions. -73- most experts agree that some research activity is -74- to keep the staff and their students in -75- with the lastest developments in their subjects. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Most students attend a university mainly to -76- the knowldge needed for their chosen -77-.Educationists believe that this aim should not be the -78- one. Universities have always aimed to produce men and women -79- judgment and wisdom as well as knowledge. For this reason, they -80-students to meet others with differing -81- and to read widely to -82- their understanding in many fields of study.-83-a secondary school course, a student should be interested enough in a subject to enjoy gaining knowledge for its own -84-.He should be prepared to -85- sacrifices to study his chosen -86-in depth. He should have an ambition to make some -87- contribution to man’s knowledge.&lt;/p&gt;
                    </title>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='412' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) at  </answer>
                            <analysis>与aim常搭配使用的介词为at，aim at意思为“目的在于，目的是”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) at  ;-;B) by  ;-;C) to    ;-;D) in</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='413' score='0'>
                            <answer>D) varies</answer>
                            <analysis>turn“变化，转变”，turn from university to university“从大学变为大学”，显然是不正确的；range“(范围) 涉及”，对这些功能的重视范围从大学到大学，这样的表达也是不正确的；move“移动”，显然不正确。只有vary最为准确，意思是“变化，有不同”，句 意“对这些功能的重视个个大学是不同的……”</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) turns;-;B) ranges ;-;C) moves;-;D) varies</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='414' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) control </answer>
                            <analysis>prospect“前景，景象”，in prospect“可以预料到(在望，有希望)”，在这里修饰前面的people不恰当；in place“在合适的位置”，in control“控制，管理”，in favour“支持，赞同”，后面要跟介词of，此处不选。虽然in place和in control都可以修饰前面的people，但结合前面的The emphasis given to each of these functions可知，只有大学的领导人才能给予这些功能不同的重视，因此选择control最为准确。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) prospect;-;B) place ;-;C) control ;-;D) favor</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='415' score='0'>
                            <answer>B) possess </answer>
                            <analysis>occupy“占据，占有”，possess“拥有，持有”，involve“包含，涉及”，spare“抽出（时间），宽恕，赦免”，空前的主语为“规模小、建校时间短的大学”，空后的宾语为“人员和设备”，选择possess最为准确。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) occupy;-;B) possess ;-;C) involve ;-;D) spare</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='416' score='0'>
                            <answer>D) vast</answer>
                            <analysis> maximum“最大（高）的，顶点的”，medium“中间的，中等的”，virtual“实质上的，实际上的”，vast“大量的，广阔的，巨大 的”，根据后面的larger institutions可推断出相比与前面的smaller and newer universities，这些机构所进行的研究项目无论在规模上还是在数量上都是vast。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) maximum;-;B) medium ;-;C) virtual ;-;D) vast</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='417' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) But </answer>
                            <analysis>该空后面句子的大体意思是说有必要获知所学科目最前沿的发展情况，空前的句子强调了规模小、建校时间短的大学在教员和设备上都匮乏，因此此处应该是转折的关系，选择But。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) But ;-;B) As  ;-;C) While ;-;D) For</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='418' score='0'>
                            <answer>B) essential</answer>
                            <analysis> natural“自然的”，essential“必不可少的，本质的”，functional“功能的，实用的”，optional“可选择的，随意的”，根据该空所在句的句意“但是大多数专家都认为，为了使师生与他们所研究的科目的最新发展保持  74  ，一些研究活动是  73  。”对比四个选项，essential最为恰当。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) natural ;-;B) essential;-;C) functional ;-;D) optional</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='419' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) touch</answer>
                            <analysis> in coordination with“与……合作”，in accordance with“按照，依照”，in touch with“保持联系，接触”，grasp“把握，抓住”，既可作名词也可作动词，没有in grasp with的表达方式。结合上体解析中该句的句意判断，选择touch最为准确，“与他们所研究的科目的最新发展保持联系”，就是说能及时地获知所研究科目 的最新发展。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) coordination;-;B) accordance;-;C) touch;-;D) grasp</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='420' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) acquire</answer>
                            <analysis>四个选项中endure“忍耐，忍受”，ensure“确保，担保”这两个是较容易排除的，因为和后面的knowledge搭配不恰当；accept“接 收”，指主动地接收某物或某种抽象的东西，此空要表达的意思是“获取知识”，通常情况下需用acquire，表示“学到，获取”，来与knowledge 搭配，而不用accept。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) acquire;-;B) accept   ;-;C) endure  ;-;D) ensure</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='421' score='0'>
                            <answer>B) profession</answer>
                            <analysis> procession“队伍，行列”，profession“职业，专业”，possession“拥有，占有”，preference“偏爱，偏好”， 根据该句的句意“大多数学生上大学主要是为他们选择的    学习知识。”可指此空选择profession最为准确。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) procession;-;B) profession;-;C) possession;-;D) preference</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='422' score='0'>
                            <answer>D) only</answer>
                            <analysis> typical“典型的，特有的”，true“真正的，真实的”，mere“纯粹的，仅仅的”，only“唯一的”，根据79空后面的judgment and wisdom as well as knowledge可推断出教育工作者一定是认为获取知识不是上大学的唯一目的，所以选择only。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) typical;-;B) true ;-;C) mere ;-;D) only</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='423' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) with  </answer>
                            <analysis>with“具有，跟，同”，under“在……之下”，on“在……上”，through“穿过，经过”，根据该句的句意“大学始终致力于培养    判断力、智慧和知识的男生和女生。”可知选择with最为恰当，指这些学生具有判断力、智慧和知识。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) with  ;-;B) under ;-;C) on  ;-;D) through</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='424' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) encourage </answer>
                            <analysis>prompt“激起，促使”，多指某事或某物刺激某人去做某事，provoke“激怒，煽动”，encourage“鼓励，支持”，anticipate “期望，预期”，空前的they指的是universities（也可以理解为大学的教师），比较四个选项，encourage最为恰当。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) prompt  ;-;B) provoke ;-;C) encourage ;-;D) anticipate</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='425' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) interests</answer>
                            <analysis>histories“历史”，expressions“表情，表达”，interests“兴趣，爱好”，curiosity作可数名词时，意思是“珍 品，古玩”，作不可数名词时，意为“好奇，好奇心”。根据该句的意思“大学鼓励学生和那些具有不同的    的人接触”可判断选择interests最为恰当。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) histories ;-;B) expressions ;-;C) interests;-;D) curiosities</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='426' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) broaden </answer>
                            <analysis> broaden“拓宽，拓广”，lengthen“使变长，使延伸”，enforce“强迫，强制，加强”，specify“指定，阐述，详细说明”，该 空所填动词的宾语为their understanding，从搭配上看broaden最为准确，可译为“加深理解”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) broaden ;-;B) lengthen ;-;C) enforce ;-;D) specify</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='427' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) After </answer>
                            <analysis> 空后的secondary school course指的是中学课程，空前的所有内容都是关于大学教育的，根据该空所在句的句意“    中学课程，一个学生应该对某一学科有足够的兴趣，以便乐于学习相关知识……”，根据前面的extending man’s knowledge，broaden their understanding等可知只有大学才能真正做到这些，基于此我们可以推断出中学的课程在于激发学生兴趣，以便学生怀着浓烈的兴趣在大学中深挖自己 所感兴趣的科目，因此选择after。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) Amid   ;-;B) Over   ;-;C) After ;-;D) Upon</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='428' score='0'>
                            <answer>D) sake</answer>
                            <analysis>for one’s own sake为固定表达，意为“为了自己的利益, 为了……的缘故”，空前的its指的是knowledge’s，此处gaining knowledge for its own sake指为了知识而获取知识，就是说怀着浓厚的兴趣为了深入学习某一门知识而学习。object“物体，目的”，course“课程，线 路”，effect“影响，作用”，注意这里的its指的是knowledge’s，object、course、effect用在这里皆不恰当。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) object   ;-;B) effect  ;-;C) course ;-;D) sake</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='429' score='0'>
                            <answer>C) make  </answer>
                            <analysis>此处考查了表示“做出牺牲做……”这一含义的短语，正确的应该是make sacrifices to do something，其他几个动词与sacrifices搭配不能表达此含义。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) take ;-;B) suffer;-;C) make  ;-;D) pay</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='430' score='0'>
                            <answer>A) field</answer>
                            <analysis>根据前文中82空后的their understanding in many fields of study可推断此空选择field最为恰当，指研究、学习的领域，该句的study his chosen field in depth正好与前文的broaden their understanding in many fields of study相对应。其他词scope“范围”，target“目标，靶子”，goal“目标，球门”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) field;-;B) target  ;-;C) scope  ;-;D) goal</questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='0' id='431' score='0'>
                            <answer>B) meaningful  </answer>
                            <analysis>四个词的意思分别为radical“根本的，激进的”，truthful“真实的，真正的”，meaningful“有意义的”，initial“最初 的，开始的”，该句的意思为“他应该有志于对人类的知识做出    贡献。”比较四个选项meaningful最为恰当。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs>A) radical;-;B) meaningful  ;-;C) truthful;-;D) initial  </questionattrs>
                            <tags> 完形填空</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            </problems>
        </block>
        <block id='24' start_time='0:5' time='5' total_num='5' total_score='0.0'>
            <base_info>
                <title>Part VI Translation </title>
                <description>Directions:	Complete the sentences by translating into English the Chinese given in brackets. Please write your translation on Answer Sheet 2.</description>
            </base_info>
            <problems>
                <problem id='70' score='0.0' types='4'>
                    <title/>
                    <category>2</category>
                    <questions>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='432' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Our efforts will pay off if the results of the research _________ .（能应用于新技术的开发）</description>
                            <answer>can be applied to the development of the new technology</answer>
                            <analysis>［考点］&lt;br&gt;① apply一词的用法。apply… to…表示“应用于；适用于”；apply for表示“申请”。&lt;br&gt;
        ② 情态动词的被动语态。
                            </analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>翻译</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='433' score='0.0'>
                            <description>I can’t boot my computer now. Something __________（一定出了毛病）with its operating system.</description>
                            <answer>must be wrong</answer>
                            <analysis>［考点］must be 推测意义句型的考查。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>翻译</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='434' score='0.0'>
                            <description>Leaving one’s job, _____________ （无论是什么工作）, is a difficult change, even for those who look forward to retiring.</description>
                            <answer>no matter what the job is/ whatever the job is</answer>
                            <analysis>［考点］① no matter what 或whatever引导的让步状语从句；② 从句中的语序问题。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>翻译</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='435' score='0.0'>
                            <description> _________（与我成长的地方相比）, this town is more prosperous and exciting.</description>
                            <answer>Compared with the place where I was brought up</answer>
                            <analysis>［考点］①分词做状语；where引导的定语从句。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>翻译</tags>
                        </question>
                        <question correct_type='3' id='436' score='0.0'>
                            <description>_________（直到他完成使命）did he realize that he was seriously ill.  </description>
                            <answer>Not until he finished his mission</answer>
                            <analysis>［考点］①not until置于句首引起的倒装句型；② mission表示“使命”。</analysis>
                            <questionattrs/>
                            <tags>翻译</tags>
                        </question>
                    </questions>
                </problem>
            </problems>
        </block>
    </blocks>
    <problem_ids/>
</paper>